An ancient evil has awoken.
The Cellar is a horror, mystery film directed by Brendan Muldowney.
When Keira Woods' daughter mysteriously vanishes in the cellar of their new house in the country, she soon discovers there is an
ancient and powerful entity controlling their home that she will have to face or risk losing her family's souls forever.
Keira, played by Elisha Cuthbert.
Brian, played by Eoin Macken.
Steven Woods, played by Dylan Fitzmaurice-Brady.
Erica, played by Tara Lee.
Michael, played by Michael-David McKernan.
Detective Brophy, played by Andrew Bennett.
The Cellar is a 2022 supernatural horror film written and directed by
Brendan Muldowney and starring Elisha Cuthbert and Eoin Macken.
It follows a family whose daughter disappears in the cellar of
the large estate they have just moved into.
The film was released via Shudder on 15 April 2022.
The film explores themes of mother, supernatural, cellar, hell, haunted house.
The tone is dark and mind_bending.